pakheaven.com 2006-10-22

# ...:::PakHeaven.com:::... -- Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement Of PakHeaven.com ! A Heaven in Web world!** **  
****  
PakHeaven.com!** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [http://www.pakheaven.com](http://www.pakheaven.com/)

**Advertisers  
**We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. 

**External Links**  
All contents and related material of this website are collected from different websites after enhancement technique. No part of this website should be copied illegally. 

**Public Forums  
**This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Data Quality / Access  
**This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [info@pakheaven.com](mailto:info@pakheaven.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: [http://www.pakheaven.com](http://www.pakheaven.com/)

**Contacting The Web Site  
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
